

NGUYEN THANH DAM

0948498651 | nguyendam5555@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-thanh-dam-808661216 | https://damnt055.github.io

District 9, Thu Duc, Ho Chi Minh

Apply my knowledge, experience and skills to complete the work of the company and the management set out. As a logical thinker, the ability to work as a team, the ability to with stand high pressure, I look forward to learning, improving my expertise and professional skills, improving myself through the company's working environment

Work Experiences

FPT Software - Ho Chi Minh

May 2023 - Jul 2023

Al Engineer Collaborator

- Travel Data Analysis using Kmeans & Catboost.
- · Ticket Analysis and Optimization.
- · Bank Customer Churn Prediction.

Freelance - sachsanhxanh.site

Apr 2023 - Jun 2023

Web Developer

· Develop an e-commerce website selling snacks using MySQL, PHP (Codeigniter)

TGA Joint stock company (Mia.vn) - Ho Chi Minh

Sep 2022 - May 2023

PHP Developer

- Participating in programming and developing support systems for the MIA.vn retail chain's business:
 - Internal management system ERP, HRM, CRM,...
 - Sales website system.

Freelance - the2percenter.com

Jan 2023 - Feb 2023

Web Developer

- Designing and implementing the front-end using HTML, CSS, jQuery, Bootstrap.
- Building CMS system using PHP, MySQL based on Codeighter framework.
- Setup, Deploy and Manage Websites on Ubuntu VPS.

FPT Software - Ho Chi Minh

Sep 2022 - Dec 2022

Al Engineer Internship

- · Collect and label data for the SoundAl project.
- · Equip yourself with more knowledge about AI and code under the guidance of teamleader

Education Level

FPT University (Đại học FPT) - District 9, Ho Chi Minh city

Oct 2019 - Sep 2023 (Expected)

Bachelor Degree in Information Technology, 8.50/10.00

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Programming Language: Golang, PHP, SQL, Python, Java, Html/Css/Javascript
- Libraries & Frameworks: Laravel, Codeinighter, Flask, Bootstrap, Jquery, Numpy, Pandas, Scikit-learn, Pytorch
- Others: MySQL, Git, Docker
- · Languages: Basic in English, Beginner in Japanese
- Certifications: Online Coursera in: Academic Skills for University Success Specialization (SSL101c), Computer Communications Specialization (NWC203c), Python for Everybody Specialization (PRP201c), AI Foundations for Everyone Specialization (AIG201c), CertNexus Certified Ethical Emerging Technologist (ITE302c), Machine Learning (AIL302m), Big Data (BDI301c), Deep Learning (DPL301m), Natural Language Processing(NLP301c)